# VICKY HERDIANSYAH ADRI

(+62) 822-5911-5329 | vickyadri103@gmail.com | github.com/vickyadri29 | linkedin.com/in/vickyadrii vickyadrii.vercel.app, Palu, Indonesia

#### **ABOUT ME**

As a Frontend Engineer, I am interested in web development and learn new technologies. I'm able to develop web applications and consume APIs. I have experience using agile methodologies and scrum to ensure that the web platform meets the company's standards for performance and reliability.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Tadulako Univeristy** 

Palu, Indonesia

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

08/2019 - 06/2023

Major in Informatics Engineering;

Relevant Coursework: Algorithms; Data Structure; Calculus; Web Basic; API; Cloud Computing.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### PT Edukasi Global Teknologi - Mau Belajar Apa

Remote, Jakarta

Part-Time | Junior Frontend Engineer

01/2023 - Present

- Build, maintain, develop new features, and improve the education platform of the Eduqat web app using Next.js.
- Collaborate with the UI/UX designer team to develop the web into code and work with backend developers to integrate the functionality and consume RESTFul API.
- Learn to write clean code, testable code, and implement agile methodologies.
- Participate with the UAT team to ensure that the platform meets the company's standards for performance and reliability.

Leverage knowledge: React.Js, Next.js, Redux, Ant Design, Styled-component, Agile Methodology

PT. Hadji Kalla

Onsite, Makassar

Internship | Web Developer Intern

07/2022 – 12/2022

- Build a web app to ensure the web will be responsive user interface and user-friendly.
- Develop a WhatsApp gateway that enables the company to broadcast messages to customers using Next.js, Tailwind, and Baileys.
- Collaborate with the UI/UX designer team to develop the web into code and work with backend developer to integrate functionality and consume RESTFul API.

Leverage knowledge: React.Js, Next.js, Javascript, Tailwind, Agile Methodology

Kodingna

Remote, Kalimantan

Internship | Frontend Web Developer Intern

06/2022 - 09/2022

- Develop a Kodingna's landing page using React.js and Tailwind.
- Learn new technical skills and gain practical experience in frontend development, design collaboration, and project management.

Leverage knowledge: React.Js, Javascript, Tailwind, Figma, Git, Agile Methodology

### Bangkit Academy by Google, GoTo, Traveloka

Remote, Jakarta

Cohort | Cloud Computing Learning Path

02/2022 - 07/2022

- Develop our website for our team capstone project.
- Build and deploy RESTFul API to our team. Deploy to Cloud Function and can be used or consumed by Mobile Development Path.

• Deploy Flask App from Machine Learning Path. Used Docker, built a container registry, and deployed to Cloud Run.

Leverage knowledge: Cloud Computing, Google Cloud Platform, Javascript, Web, Firebase, Git.

### **ORGANIZATION**

### **Google Developer Student Club Universitas Tadulako**

Curriculum Core Team

Palu, Indonesia 11/2023 – Present

- Create a course for our member GDSC
- be a mentor

### **Programming Tadulako**

Member

Palu, Indonesia 11/2021 – 01/2023

- Be a mentor of web development
- Develop our web app
- Create design posts on our social media

## **ACADEMIC PROJECTS**

### **Web App Programming Tadulako**

- Design UI on Figma
- Develop a web app using React typescript
- Consume RESTFul API to show our events on events pages
  Leverage knowledge: React typescript, Tailwind, Figma.

#### **Medical Robot Assistant**

- Design UI on Figma
- Consume RESTFul API from Backend Developer
- Develop and design a better UI for this web app using React.js

Leverage knowledge: ReactJS, Tailwind.css, Figma.

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- **Technical Skills**: Javascript, Typescript, ReactJS, Next.JS, NodeJS, Tailwind, Styled-component, Ant-Design, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase.
- Languages: Fluent in Indonesia; Intermediate in English.
- Tools: Git, Bash, Jira/Trello